[ED]
Ooh! Oh! That was amazing!
I think I've flown the farthest!
That was amazing!
Oh, my gosh, I can't see it anymore.
Hello, I'm Miku Ichinose.
Yes, I'd like to start playing golf today.
I'm thinking?
I've been interested in golf for a while.
I've always wanted to start playing golf.
I've been thinking about taking up golf for a while now, and this project has given me the chance to try it.
I would like to do my best from now on.
I hope to play golf with Mr. Higuchi, my senior, someday.
I hope to be able to play golf with Mr. Higuchi, one of my seniors.
I'm going to practice hard!
And what a surprise!
We have a special guest today!
Mr. Suganuma, the pro. Please.
Please, please, please.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
What a surprise. Today is the first time...
We have a special guest today.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy. Thank you.
I hear you like Miyasaka 46.
That's right, I really like them.
And Miki is my favorite.
I'm so glad. Is that so?
Yes. You missed my live performance the other day.
I'm your favorite.
That's great. Thank you.
So today...
I'm going to try my hand at golf.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
I'm counting on you.
Can I call you Miku-chan?
Of course I'd like that.
What do you call me then?
Can I call you Nana-chan?
Is that okay?
I'll call you Miku-chan.
Nana, please.
I'm a little new at this.
I went to practice a little bit the other day.
Is it okay if I ask you to watch me?
Yes, I'm fine.
Are you okay with that?
I'm not sure if I can hit it.
Yes, sir.
Oh! It hit!
But it's flying straight.
Oh! I hit it!
You should stand a little closer.
Closer? Closer?
Too close.
That's about right.
You're going to hit it and then you're done, so try swinging away.
Like you're swinging away.
Oh, wow.
It flew so fast!
It's a mask!
I can feel it swinging away. I see.
It's coming up a little too high.
I think I should go straight up a little bit.
Straight up.
Oh, wow!
I hit it!
It's flying pretty well.
All of your advice is spot on.
It's flying really well.
But I really don't like it when
If I get too much praise.
I get carried away and stop flying.
That's the way I am.
I'm like that.
Oh, that's too bad.
It's too bad.
But you're much more in touch than at first.
Really?
I want to see you typing.
- Can I hit? Can I? Yes, please.
Then hit it like this.
I'll hit.
Oh, my God.
Oops.
A little bit.
Like this.
It's not like this, is it?
What?
Wow!
But you usually dance, don't you, KAMIKU-chan?
Dancing requires a lot of physical sensation, doesn't it?
That's why you hit golf shots with your body.
I'm sure it will fly when you get good at it.
Really?
I think so.I think it will fly.
How old were you when you started playing golf?
Five.
Five?
Five years old.
So you can start at five?
Not at all, but I did it when I was little.
That's amazing.
Wow, that's too much!
Oh!
Oh! But you're right.
Yeah.
When you raise it...
It's a little shaky.
You should be more conscious of your axis.
You should be more conscious of your body.
My body gets shaky.
So, the soles of your feet... hold on tight.
It's like spinning on an axis.
It's difficult.
If I say too much, you'll lose track, won't you?
Oh, wow! But I feel like my swing is getting stronger.
You really understand everything, don't you?
That's amazing.
I've only practiced indoors.
Compared to that, it feels better outside?
It's a little more comfortable, too.
It's a little more comfortable.
Wow!
That's great.
Oh! That's great! That's the biggest jump I've ever made!
Just kind of open your legs and straighten up and shake it out, and you'll be fine.
Wow! It's warm!
It's cold!
23... almost 3?
No, almost 3.
Congratulations! Thank you very much.
I'm...
I'm 19 now. I'll be in my 20s.
What's your favorite food?
Food? Well, I don't know...
But... shrimp and chili...
Surprisingly good!
It's good. You're right.
I've been craving it every day lately.
I'm addicted to it... Do you like spicy food?
As long as it's not too spicy.
So it's okay? Kimchi...
I love it.
Korean food...
I love Korean food.
I see.
What do you like? Rice...
Udon?
Udon!
What kind of udon do you like?
Anything... I prefer them hot.
I see... That's true.
Udon's good.
It's not that spicy these days.
Is it good? Delicious.
Shrimp chili... Do you like shrimp mayo too?
I like shrimp mayo.
Shrimp mayo is good.
But I didn't like it very much.
The first time I tried it...
It's the hardest thing to make.
Of course. I tried it.
I want to try it.
Thank you.
What's it like?
Hold on a second.
Thank you very much.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow, that's hard.
You can go to the course now.
Not at all...
I want to see it.
You want to hit it?
May I?
Yes, please.
Here we go.
Like this?
Oh, my God! I can't see the ball anymore.
There's an aura overflowing.
I mean, it's so cool!
It's so cool!
It's the posture that makes the difference, isn't it?
It's true, your posture.
Maybe you should put a little more front weight on it.
Front weight?
About that much.
You look really good.
Looks good?
Looks good.
Oh, my God.
How did you fly so high?
I just hit the ground a little bit.I just hit the ground a little bit.
No, it's okay, it's fine.
And then you just swing away.
Swing it, swing it, swing it, swing it.
You're gonna hit the ground.
There it is!
Do your muscles ache the day after golf?
I was in a state of shock.
For three or four days.
What? So it's bad tomorrow?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
I'm scared.
It's like... you're going to swing out as hard as you can.
It's hard to hit the ball, so...
It's hard to hit the ball, so... you have to swing as hard as you can.
I see. The ball was right where I was swinging.
Heh heh heh.
Heh heh heh
- Oh! Oh! Oh, yeah! Oh, my God! That was amazing!
- I think I've flown the most! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God! That's great! Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh! Oh, wow! That was amazing! I think that's the most I've flown! That's great!
It's getting better.
But it's so powerful, I swear, if I keep working on it, it's gonna fly just fine.
Oh, wow! That's great! That's the best!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
That's great.
Oh! That's great!
Oh, wow.
But it's great!
Is there ever a day when you don't feel like
Is there a day when you don't feel like this person? On the contrary.
On days when I don't...
I have them.
About twice a year.
Twice?
On the days you don't.
That's amazing.
That's too much.
But are there days when you don't dance?
There are days when I don't dance.
Do you have days when you don't dance?
Yes, I do.
Oh, wow.
Do you dance today?
Today is a no-dance day.
But I'll go home and dance.
Do you practice at home?
Yes, at home.
Quite a bit.
Like on "A Star is Born.
There's a lot of dancing on the show.
So you dance a lot.
We dance a lot.
That's for sure.
Is that your first goal?
On the course.
I don't know... 140.
One hundred and forty.
Well, I'd be happy with that.
140?
If it's your first time and it's 140...
How soon can you dance?
I averaged about 71 last year.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
70 is 100 kills, that's amazing!
That's right.
That's amazing!
Seventy.
Best or something?
The best I've ever had was 64.
That's really great.
Oh, no.
Aah!
Hahahaha
It's gonna be so hard to keep up, probably.
Hard?
- Like straight up? Straight up?
Straight up.
Oh!
Now that's good, right?
That's good.
First pitch.
Oh!
Aaah!
That's good.
How's that?
One is good.
Uh, one is fine.
Hee-hee-hee-hee.
It's okay. It's okay.
Shake it out.
You did your best, Miku.
Hee-hee-hee!
Wow.
What?
It didn't feel like hitting a ball.It's not like hitting a ball.
It's like... like swinging through the air.
Shake it out.
Oh.
Oh!
Good job.
All right!
You want to keep going?
That's good.
Shall we continue?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Uh-huh.
How's it going?
Oh, no? Bad?
Am I not cheering enough?
Then I'll cheer for you.
What? Wait a minute.
Wait, wait.
Summer...
Riku-chan, I'm rooting for you.
Riku-chan!
Riku-chan, hang in there!
Can you make it?
Riku-chan!
Wait a minute!
I'm sorry.
You're smiling.
You're laughing.
Oh, the first pitch?
No, no, no, no, no.
- What? No? No? No? No? No? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Uh-uh.
Ahh!
I'm already guessing, so please be nice to him
Uh-huh
I'm getting rather confused at all
I want to shake it off and put all my strength into the soles of my feet
I want to do a little bit of shimputing.
Yuki-chan, hang in there.
Good luck, Yuki-chan!
Aaah!
Aaah! Delicious.
Oh!
Oh, you passed.
It's a good one.
Good for you.
Best of the best!
That was great!
Perfect!
I'm so happy.
I mean, I'm really...
I don't know, I just...
It's so close at hand.
I really feel better than when I did it indoors.
It felt really good.
It feels good to hit a good spot, doesn't it?
And all the time...
That praise.
Stretch me out.
You're my sister.
I'd like you to be my friend.
Thank you.
I'd like to go to the game.
I'd like to go watch.
Is that okay?
Please let me cheer for you.
I'll be there to cheer for Riku-chan.
Really?
We'll support each other and do our best.
Let's do our best!
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, by the way...
Today, I'm going to talk to the real Muffler.
I was able to finish the day's practice
I was able to finish a full day of practice
It was my first time outside.
It's different from inside.
It was great!
The wind felt so good
It was really fun to play.
I want to keep practicing
I want to keep practicing hard.
From now on
I want to practice hard enough
I want to practice hard enough to get out on the course.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Bye bye!